### LALETH T R

trlaleth@gmail.com | +916383649494 https://www.linkedin.com/in/LalethTR | https://github.com/laleth 385, Kamarajar Road, Athani (PO), Anthiyur (TK), Erode (DT), TamilNadu - 638502

#### Summary

I have over 3 years of experience working in Software engineering industry. Currently, I work as a software development engineer at HTC Global Service, providing technical support for PeopleSoft applications as Application Lead.I am very much interested and excited to build a career in Full-Stack Web Development. Currently, I am practicing Full Stack projects.

# Professional Experience

#### **Software Engineer**

HTC Global Service | Nov 2020 - Nov 2023

- Technical Support for Peoplesoft Purchasing Application.
- Responding to Client Mails and Fixing the Issues.
- IBM DB2 and Mainframe Systems Support.
- Developing Python Script for Automation Tasks.
- Fixing bugs in existing code and implementing it to production.
- Incident and Change management.

# Personal Experience

#### Vector India | Jul 2019 - Jan 2020

Vector India is a private institute provides a knowledge on C and Embedded etc.

#### Guvi | Mar 2023 - Nov 2023

Guvi is a online program that provides hands-on experience in Full-Stack projects and technologies using React, Node, MongoDB, Git etc. and developed a meal finder app using React JS.

https://meal-finder-henna.vercel.app/

#### **Education**

#### Bachelor of Engineering - Electronics and Communication Engineering

2015 – 2019 | Karpagam College of Engineering, Coimbatore

Class: First Class

#### Skills

- Web Development
- IBM Mainframes
- Databases
- JavaScript
- React JS
- Node JS
- MongoDB

## Languages

Tamil Native or Bilingual proficiency

English Professional working proficiency

### **INTERESTS**

Travelling

Badminton